No, no. You've always wanted to send your
food back in a restaurant. Here's your chance.
- That's okay. I just won't eat them.
- Don't be ridiculous. Waiter?
(Waiter:)Everything all right?
(Lucy:)Uh, yeah. Everything all right with you?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
- Okay, thanks, bye.
- Hold on.
(Raj:)Isn't there something else
you wanted to tell him?
No, it's fine. He's from a different country.
He doesn't understand our ways.
(Raj:)Don't be silly. Just tell him.
(Lucy:)I have to go to the bathroom. And it's not
because the crab cakes are funky.
- So you're okay here?
- Uh, yeah, sorry. She's just a little shy.
(Raj:)The first time we met, she was so nervous...
(Raj:)...she climbed out
a bathroom window to get away.